[
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "alert(typeof(NaN));",
        "choices": ["number", "object", "string", "function"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "number"
    },
    {
        "question": "You canâ€™t delete variables declared with var keyword by 'delete' operator.",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "alert(typeof([1, 2]) != (typeof {obg:23}));",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
    },
    {
        "question": "JS numbers are always stored as double precision floating point numbers.",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "alert(0.1 + 0.2 == 0.3);",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
    },
    {
        "question": "What function is used to merge arrays?",
        "choices": ["concat()", "merge()", "array_merge()", "add()"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "concat()"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "function mlt(a, b) {\n  if(!(a && b)) {\n    return 0;\n  } else if(b == 1) {\n    return a;\n  } else {\n    return (a + mlt(a, b - 1));\n  }\n}\nconsole.log(mlt(3, 11));\nconsole.log(mlt(7, 1));",
        "type": "input",
        "correctAnswer": "337"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "(function(){\n  alert(typeof arguments);\n})();",
        "choices": ["object", "function", "undefined", "null"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "object"
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the numbers that are present in the output.",
        "description": "for(let i = 0; i < 100; i ++)\n  if(i % 10 == i - 10)\n    document.write(i + ',');",
        "choices": ["14", "17", "27", "9"],
        "type": "select",
        "correctAnswer": ["14", "17"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "var a = 5 && 8;\nvar b = 5 || 8;\nconsole.log(a + b);",
        "type": "input",
        "correctAnswer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "console.log((true+false)>2+true);",
        "choices": ["true", "false", "error"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "const mul = x => y => x * y;\nconst res = mul(2)(5);\nconsole.log(res);",
        "type": "input",
        "correctAnswer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is this code valid?",
        "description": "a = 5;\nalert(a);",
        "choices": ["yes", "no"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "console.log((![]+[])[1]);",
        "type": "input",
        "correctAnswer": "a"
    }
]
